webtvhub.com 2019-08-31

# Privacy Policy – Web TV Hub

WebTVHub recognizes that privacy is very important and that your personal data should remain private. Our privacy policy is as follows: 

## Scope

This policy applies to all the products and services that WebTVHub provides, including but not limited to the WebTVHub website. 

## Information We Collect

#### Website Logs

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes and records certain information that your web browser provides to us. This includes information such as: – web request – browser type – internet protocol address – browser language – date and time of your request – length of your stay – the referral web page This information is used to monitor the usage of our service and improve our service. 

#### Communication

When you communicate with WebTVHub by email, telephone, postal letter, a comment on our website, a post on our bulletin board, online chat, or other similar communication we may record all information. This is to improve our services, process your inquiry and deal with your request. Your individual information including your email address, name and telephone number will not be passed on to any third parties without your prior written consent. **Commenting** When commenting on the site we may send you a personal email to ask you a question if your comment was of particular interest to us. 

#### WebTVHub Email Subscription

The information you provide when signing up to our email subscription will not be passed onto any third parties without your permission. We will send you regular updates with news and stories from the site. You can opt out of the mailing list at any time by following the unsubscribe link in any of the emails we send you. 

#### Links

Occasionally WebTVHub will present links on our websites that keep track of whether you click the links and any actions which follow. We use this information to improve the quality of our service and provide customized content and advertising. 

#### Cookies

We may use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same advertisements, customize Web page content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. You can choose not to accept cookies from our site by changing the settings in your web browser. However, some of the functions of our site may not work correctly. **Google Ads**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Changes to Policy and Choice over your Personal Information

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. WebTVHub will allow you to access your personal information, correct your data is it is inaccurate or delete data should you require it. This does not apply if we are otherwise required to retain your data by law, need your data for legitimate business purposes, or it requires a disproportionate technical effort. You can decline to provide WebTVHub with certain personal information at anytime. However, we may not be able to provide you with certain services as a result. 

## Security

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
